tagdiv.com 2019-10-21

# Privacy Policy - tagDiv support

_Last update: September 16, 2019_

Thank you for visiting tagDiv. Privacy is a big concern for us and we take it very seriously. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to learn more about the way we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users.

When you register to the support forum or when you navigate our website at tagdiv.com some personal data will be sent to our servers. You can at any time revoke your consent and request us to permanently delete any data that is collected. To do that, please email us to contact@tagdiv.com

WHAT DATA IS COLLECTED

We collect personal information directly when you provide it to us (user-names, member names, email addresses, The Envato purchase code for the item, IP addresses, and other contact details, photos, support queries, forum comments), and automatically as you navigate through the Site (web analytics data provided by Google and Facebook)

WHAT DATA WE SHARE WITH THIRD PARTIES

We share with Google’s Analytics service the following data:

  * the Google provided cookie
  * the IP address that connected to our server
  * page view data (the url that was visited)

We share with Facebook’s Analytics service the following data:

  * the Facebook provided cookie
  * the IP address that connected to our server
  * page view data (the URL that was visited)

**CONSENT**

If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this policy, please do not provide any personal information to tagDiv. If you have provided personal information to us and no longer consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please notify tagDiv to contact@tagdiv.com.

**THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS**

This privacy policy covers tagDiv’s approach on the personally identifiable information collected through the website owned and operated by tagDiv. This privacy policy does not apply to the practices used by third-party companies for whom tagDiv has no ownership or control, or of persons that tagDiv does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors and any third-party websites to which the website may link.

**COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We collect certain personal information from you when you sign up to our services that can be used to identify you, such as your name, e-mail address, user name, purchase code and any other relevant information for the purpose of providing you with our service or which you provide to us voluntarily.

You can visit our website without disclosing any identifiable information. But when you visit our site, we may collect non-identifying information from you, such as your IP address, referring URL, browser, operating system, cookie information and Internet Service Provider.

By accessing the services of tagDiv and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

**USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We may use your information to:

• Enhance or improve user experience, our site or our service.

• Send e-mails about our site or respond to inquiries.

• Send e-mails and updates about tagDiv, including our e-mail newsletter.

**INSTAGRAM ACCOUNT APP AUTHORIZATION**

If you own a tagDiv theme license and want to connect an Instagram account with your website, you need to authorize the tagDiv WordPress Theme App to use it. We may collect data regarding your account, such as the logo, display name, username, profile image, number of followers, or published content. All the data collected by authorizing tagDiv WordPress Theme App to access your Instagram account will only be used by tagDiv on your behalf. By using the app and voluntarily allowing access to your own Instagram account, you consent to the use of the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. The collected data is used for your own benefit and won’t be shared with any third parties.

**ACCESSING, EDITING AND REMOVING YOUR INFORMATION**

Users may be able to review and edit the personal information they have provided to us by logging into their account on the website. Although most changes may occur immediately, information may still be stored in a web browser’s cache. We take no responsibility for stored information in your cache.

**COOKIES**

We use cookies to remember your preferences and track advertisements. You acknowledge that we have informed you of our use of cookies and that you consent to our use of cookies in relation to your computer system.

**INFORMATION SHARING & DISCLOSURE**

tagDiv will not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**SECURITY**

Your information is protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas of our websites, as identified on the site, tagDiv may use industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. We also safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access through access control procedures and physical security measures. It is in our interest to keep our website secure, but we recommend that you use anti-virus software, firewalls and other precautions to protect yourself from security threats.

**MODIFICATION TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

At any time, without notice to you, tagDiv may amend this policy. When it does, we will revise the “last update” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. Please review this privacy policy periodically. Your continued use of the site after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.
